One mistake. One mistake out of so many. So many others.
Babylon 5: Thirdspace is a action, science fiction,
adventure film directed by Jesús Salvador Treviño.
Susan Ivanova discovers a derelict spaceship in hyperspace.
They tow it back to Babylon 5, then strange things start happening.
People are being telepathically taken over by aliens from another (third)space.
Capt. John J. Sheridan, played by Bruce Boxleitner.
Susan Ivanova, played by Claudia Christian.
Delenn, played by Mira Furlan.
Elizabeth Trent, played by Shari Belafonte.
Vir Cotto, played by Stephen Furst.
Lyta Alexander, played by Patricia Tallman.
Babylon 5: Thirdspace is a 1998 American made-for-television film
that is part of the Babylon 5 science fiction universe.
It was written by J.
Michael Straczynski and directed by Jesús Salvador Treviño.
The movie was originally shown on July 19, 1998 on the TNT cable network, during the run of season five
(originally being shown between "Movements of Fire and Shadow" and "The Fall of Centauri Prime").
In addition to members of the regular cast of the Babylon 5 TV series, it
features the notable guest-stars Shari Belafonte (playing Dr.
Elizabeth Trent) and William Sanderson (reprising the role of
"Deuce" that he played in the episode "Grail").
The horror-based story, which ties into the Shadow/Vorlon plotline, centers on the return of an ancient
and overwhelming alien force which had once attempted to destroy life in the Milky Way.
The film explores themes of flying saucer, fight,
artifact, space centre, based on tv series.
The tone is thought_provoking.